Gerardo Arrieta

Frontend and Backend Developer

Barquisimeto, Venezuela (GMT-4)
58) 424 5823137
gerardojao@gmail.com
https://linkedin.com/gerardojao
https://gerardojao.vercel.app/

I am a Frontend Developer with two years of experience with Vanilla Javascript and React.JS (constantly learning). Also I am Backend Developer since 9 months ago and my experience is based on .NET and SQL SERVER. I'm willing to learn new technologies as I am characterized by being self-taught and in constant professional and personal growth. Currently I am improving REACT.JS, .Net and SQL Server. I'm looking for a remote and international job for now, and I would prefer a job as a frontend developer but if the opportunity is related to Backend, I'll take it without hesitation.

EXPERIENCE

T&M CONSULTING

Backend Developer (HEICREDIT) — March, 2022 - Present

- Construction of part of the database modeling with SQL SERVER.
- Construction of the models and controllers for the correct operation of the API.
- In this project my accounting knowledge helped to unlock the continuation of the project, as one sprint was based on a financial calculator. And the construction of the models and controllers that corresponded to me helped to minimize the delivery time of the project.

Tech Stack: .NET, SQL SERVER.

Backend Developer (AMSTEL ULTRA) — October, 2021 - February, 2022

- Construction of part of the database modeling with SQL SERVER.
- Construction of the models and controllers for the correct operation of the API.
- With my contribution we were able to reduce the project delivery times.

Tech Stack: .NET, SQL SERVER.

T&M CONSULTING — September, 2021 - October, 2021

Trainee Backend Developer — September, 2021 - October 2021

- Read the documentation about an API in .NET.
- Learn about SQL SERVER gueries.
- Preparing endpoints to integrate in the Frontend

Tech Stack: .Net, SQL SERVER, Vue.JS, GIT.

PROJECTS

Freelances Projects -

https://singer-biography.netlify.app/- 2022', https://aaconsultores.github.io/website/ - 2021

• With technologies such as Vanilla Javascript or REACT JS I have been able to build some websites both personal and for a client's request, even using HTML, CSS and/or some preprocessors. **Tech Stack:** REACT.JS, CSS, Bootstrap, GIT.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Intermediate: HTML, CSS, Javascript.

Frameworks and Tools: Intermediate: REACT.JS, .NET CORE, FIGMA, SASS, GIT.

Data Base: Intermediate: MySQL, SQL SERVER.

Agile: SCRUM

Languages: Intermediate: English; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

Yacambu University – Cabudare, Lara. Master in Business and Financial Management May 2015. **Yacambu University** – Cabudare, Lara. Bachelor's Degree in Public Accounting, December 2012.

CERTIFICATIONS

Personal Branding – PLATZI. 2022.

Learn SCRUM - LinkedIn. 2022.

Web Development Fundamentals - LinkedIn. 2022.

Responsive Web Design - FreeCodeCamp. 2021.

